<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="sample.css"?>>
<!---->
<sample>
  <page1>
  <h1>See discussions, stats, and author profiles for this publication at<href>: https://www.researchgate.net/publication/303523871</href></h1>
  <h2>ECLAT Algorithm for Frequent Item sets Generation</h2>
  <article>Article · January 2014</article>
  <citations>CITATIONS<NO1></NO1>17</citations>
  <reads>READS<NO2>15,678</NO2></reads>
  <author>
    <id>1</id>
    <h3>author:</h3>
    <name>Urvashi Bansal</name>
    <auhtor1>National institute of Technology Jalandhar</auhtor1>
    <distrubation>14 PUBLICATIONS</distrubation>
    <copies>85 CITATIONS</copies>
  </author>
  <profile>SEE PROFILE</profile>
  <para>All content following this page was uploaded by Urvashi Bansal on 29 December 2016.</para>
  <p1>The user has requested enhancement of the downloaded file</p1>
</page1>
<page2>
  <h1>International Journal of Computer Systems (ISSN: 2394-1065), Volume 01– Issue 03, December, 2014 
Available at http://www.ijcsonline.com/</h1>
<h2>ECLAT Algorithm for Frequent Itemsets Generation </h2>
<writter>Manjit Kaur , Urvashi Grag</writter>
<branch>Computer Science and Technlogy</branch>
<university>Lovely Professional University</university>
<location>Phagwara, Punjab, India. </location>
<side>Abstract<p>The main aim of the research is to generate a new ideas to generate a frequent itemset. Data mining is process of 
extracting useful information from different sources. Frequent item sets are those items which are frequently occurred. 
So we use various algorithms for this purpose. Eclat algorithm is data mining algorithm which is used to find frequent 
items from large amount of database .but apriori algorithm has some limitations so we will try to remove those 
limitations. In apriori algorithm we need to scan database again and again for finding frequent itemsets, This limitation 
is reduced by using vertical dataset in eclat. It reduces access time. </p></side>
<side1>Keywords:<p> Eclat algorithm, vertical database. </p></side1>
<intro>I INTRODUCTION
<p>In current scenario, the requirements of the database are
large respectively. There is drawback in earlier developed
algorithm is that generate a frequent item sets and it
generates candidates ser then there is need to parse the
database only once. But in this paper, the researcher tries to
reduce the scanning time if database is large. The main rule
of data mining is to discover all the items that have support
and confidence greater than or equal to given minimum
support and confidence. Data mining is also known as
knowledge discovery. It means that it helps the shopkeeper
to improve the business strategy to understand which items
are frequently demanded by particular customer. It helps in
better business environment. Data mining is method of
extracting the useful information and knowledge from very
large amount of data. Eclat algorithms generate frequent
items only once. Frequent itemsets are those items which
are frequently occur in the database. There are number of
algorithms for finding frequent itemsets. Apriori, is basic
algorithm for finding frequent itemsets. But it take more
time for finding the frequent itemsets, It needs to scan the
database again and again which is time consuming process.
In this algorithm we need to calculate support and
confidence, so eclat algorithm is developed to remove the
limitations of Apriori, algorithm. Eclat algorithm uses
vertical database. By which it need to scan the database
only once. </p></intro>
<A>A. Market basket analysis
<p></p>Market basket analysis is process of finding the buying
habits of people. Market basket analysis is very useful term
for improving business strategies. Market basket analysis is
a data mining techniques for finding the association</A>
</page2>

</sample>